Jamie Joseph Heiney

Dangerous and Effective Spy

About Me

Highly skilled and experienced spy with a track record of completing missions with precision and efficiency. I am dedicated to my work and capable of adapting to any situation. Strongly believe in completing all tasks with utmost confidentiality and professionalism.

Skills

- · Bank & Credit Card Reconciliation
- QuickBooks (Enterprise and Online)
- Google Sheets
- Excel Cash Flow Management
- · Budgeting and Financial Planning
- · Excellent communication
- Simplification of complex topics

Experience

Accountant at Alpha Capital LLC

Dec 2019 - May 2022

- Served as an accountant for several capital funding companies, managing all their bookkeeping needs. Including creating chart of
 accounts, bank reconciliation. Organized, formatted, and imported large amounts of data from CRMS, other software and google
 sheets.
- Designed and implemented a comprehensive loan tracking system using multiple interlinked Google Sheets and Google App
 Scripts. The system allowed owners, salespeople, and outside investors to view and update vital information about current and
 former deals, with multiple permission levels and an intuitive UI.
- Utilized the accounting system for multiple companies owned by Alpha Capital and provided consulting services to other companies.

Nursing Home Game Creator at Games 4 Life

Feb 2017 - Feb 2019

- Developed interactive group games for elderly care facilities to address the lack of stimulating and engaging content for elders.
- Grew client base to over 30 nursing homes and hundreds of happy users.
- Managed accounts receivable and gained a broad understanding of business and management.

AP Regional Manager at Beyond Healthcare LLC

Jan 2015 - Mar 2017

- Oversaw AP transactions and personnel for four nursing homes.
- Negotiated with vendors for more favorable contracts.
- Maintained all accounts payable reports, spreadsheets, and files.
- Acted as a liaison between corporate and nursing home accounts payable departments.
- Managed emails and website domains for the corporate staff.

Education

Certificate in Accounting Foundations Accounting Foundations: Bookkeeping QuickBooks

Online Essential Training QuickBooks Pro Essential Training Yeshiva Toras Chaim High School

Diploma

May 2008, 3.4 GPA

Dual Enrollment Florida International University Accounting Course: Accounting Coach course by Harold Averkamp Tested and received

Contact: 305-801-7497